Guide to the Stanford Authors Videorecordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford authors videorecordings
1995-1998
V0189
Stanford Channel (Television station: Stanford, Calif.)
3.75 Linear feet 30 videotapes (VHS)
This series is primarily book readings by Stanford professors, administrators, and students from their recently published works. Included are Eavan Boland, Warren Christopher, Carl Djerassi, Paul Ehrlich, John L'Heureux, Dale Maharidge, Gilbert Sorrentino, Irvin Yalom, and Marilyn Yalom.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, 1999.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Stanford Channel is managed by Stanford University's Information Technology Systems and Services (ITSS), specifically Communication Services. Its broadcasts include telecourses, original programs, lectures, conferences, and Stanford sports events.
Description of the Collection
This series is primarily book readings by Stanford professors, administrators, and students from their recently published works. Included are Eavan Boland, Warren Christopher, Carl Djerassi, Paul Ehrlich, John L'Heureux, Dale Maharidge, Gilbert Sorrentino, Irvin Yalom, and Marilyn Yalom.
Access Terms
Boland, Eavan.; Boland, Eavan.; Christopher, Warren.; Christopher, Warren.; Djerassi, Carl; Ehrlich, Paul R.; L'Heureux, John.; Maharidge, Dale.; Sorrentino, Gilbert.; Sorrentino, Gilbert.; Stanford Channel (Television station: Stanford, Calif.); Stanford University -- General subdivision--Faculty.;; Yalom, Irvin D., 1931-; Yalom, Marilyn; Authors, American--20th century.; Videorecordings.
Collection Contents
- Videos
  - Boland, Eavan. “An Origin Like Water.” (February 1996), V189.1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Burns, Stewart. “Daybreak of Freedom.” (November 1997), V189.2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Carson, Clayborne. “A Knock at Midnight: Inspiration from the Great Sermons of M.L.K. Jr. (May 1998), V189.3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Chang, Gordon. “Morning Glory, Evening Shadow.” (February 1997), V189.4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Christopher, Warren. “In the Stream of History: Shaping Foreign Policy for a New Era.” (October 1998), V189.5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Cotera, Maria Eugenia. “Caballero: An Historical Novel.” (May 1996), V189.6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Djerassi, Carl. “Marx Deceased.” (November 1996), V189.7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Duignan, Peter. “Contemporary Europe and the Atlantic Alliance.” (May 1998), V189.8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Eisen, Arnold. “Taking Hold of the Torah: Jewish Commitment and Community.” (December 1997), V189.9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Ehrlich, Paul. “Betrayal of Science and Reason.” (October 1996), V189.10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Felstiner, John. “Ear to the Ground.” (November 1997), V189.11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Fetter, Jean. “Reflections on 100,000 Admissions Decisions at Stanford.” (May 1995), V189.12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Gunther, Gerald. “Learned Hand: The Man and the Judge.” (October 1995), V189.13; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Jackson, Kennel. “America is Me.” (February 1996), V189.14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Levenstein (ed.), Enkelis & Olsen. “On Our Own Terms: Portraits of Women Business Leaders.” (November 1995), V189.15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - L’Heureux, John. “The Handmaid of Desire.” (October 1996), V189.16; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - L’Heureux, John & Nancy Packer. “Celebrating 50 Years of Creative Writing at Stanford.” (February 1996), V189.17; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Maharidge, Dale. “The Coming White Minority.” (October 1996), V189.18; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - “Making More Waves: New Writing by Asian-American Women.” (February 1998), V189.19; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Naficy, Mariam. “The Fast Track.” (October 1998), V189.20; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Ornstein, Robert. “Right Mind: Making Sense of the Hemispheres.” (November 1997), V189.21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Packer, Nancy. “Jealous Hearted Me.” (May 1997), V189.22; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Reeves, Byron. “The Media Equation: How People Treat Computers, Television and New Media…” (October 1996), V189.23; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Roberts, Dorothy. “Killing the Black Body: Race, Reproduction and the Meaning of Liberty.” (February 1998), V189.24; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Rock, Pete. “This is the Place.” (April 1997), V189.25; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Sorrentino, Gilbert. “The Orangery” (October 1995), V189.26; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Winograd, Terry. “Bringing Design to Software.” (May 1996), V189.27; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Yalom, Irvin. “Lying on the Couch.” (October 1996), V189.28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Yalom, Marilyn. “History of the Breast.”, V189.29; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Zelikow, Philip. “Germany Unified and Europe Transformed: A Study in Statecraft.” (October 1995), V189.30; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)